Class of 1913 Records, 1909-1980
Smith College Archives
Class of 1913 Records
1909-1980
Smith College. Class of 1913.
RG 80 UUID:832a1d85-0525-420e-bce9-0e59439d0685
43 boxes (26.5 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection is in 43 boxes and contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1913.
The Class of 1913 was the thirty-fourth entering class and the thirty-fourth graduating class of Smith College.
The Class of 1913 records, 1909-1980, contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1913, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, questionnaires, and other memorabilia. The Class Secretary's files also contain individual biographical information.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1913 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Baccalaureate 1913 (Box 1817, Folder 1)
- Distinguished Members 1949-1950 (Box 1817, Folder 2)
- Clippings 1913 (Box 1817, Folder 3)
- Clippings-Hampshire Gazette, June 17 1913 (Box 1817, Folder 4)
- Class Secretary-Obituaries (Box 1817, Folder 5)
- Commencement 1913 (Box 1817, Folder 6)
- Commencement Music 1913 (Box 1817, Folder 7)
- Commencement Photographs 1913 (Box 1817, Folder 8)
- Constitution undated (Box 1817, Folder 9)
- County Fair 1912 (Box 1817, Folder 10)
- Freshman Frolic 1909 (Box 1817, Folder 11)
- Freshman Grind 1909 (Box 1817, Folder 12)
- Freshman Handbook 1909 (Box 1817, Folder 13)
- Groups 1909-1913 (Box 1817, Folder 14)
- Hoop Rolling 1913 (Box 1817, Folder 15)
- Ivy Day 1913 (Box 1817, Folder 16)
- Ivy Day Photographs 1913 (Box 1817, Folder 17)
- Junior Frolic 1912 (Box 1818, Folder 1)
- Junior Prom 1912 (Box 1818, Folder 2)
- Junior Prom-Garden Party 1912 (Box 1818, Folder 3)
- Class Letters 1923-1944 (Box 1818, Folder 4)
- Class Letters 1945-1964 (Box 1818, Folder 5)
- Class Letters 1965-1980 (Box 1818, Folder 6)
- Seal Emblem undated (Box 1818, Folder 7)
- Senior Dramatics 1913 (Box 1818, Folder 8)
- Senior Dramatics-Photographs 1913 (Box 1818, Folder 9)
- Senior Reception 1913 (Box 1818, Folder 10)
- Class Supper 1913 (Box 1818, Folder 11)
- Sophomore Reception 1911 (Box 1818, Folder 12)
- Songs undated (Box 1818, Folder 13)
- Christmas Vespers 1913 (Box 1818, Folder 14)
- Class Letters-A-B 1919-1921 (Box 1819, Folder 1)
- Class Letters-C-D 1919-1921 (Box 1819, Folder 2)
- Class Letters-E-G 1919-1921 (Box 1819, Folder 3)
- Class Letters-H-K 1919-1921 (Box 1819, Folder 4)
- Class Letters-L-M 1919-1921 (Box 1819, Folder 5)
- Class Letters-O-R 1919-1921 (Box 1819, Folder 6)
- Class Letters-S-T 1919-1921 (Box 1819, Folder 7)
- Class Letters-U-Z 1919-1921 (Box 1819, Folder 8)
- Class Secretary's Records-A-B (Box 1819, Folder 9)
- Class Secretary's Records-C-D (Box 1819, Folder 10)
- Class Secretary's Records-E-G (Box 1819, Folder 11)
- Class Secretary's Records-H-K (Box 1819, Folder 12)
- Class Secretary's Records-L-N (Box 1819, Folder 13)
- Class Secretary's Records-O-R (Box 1819, Folder 14)
- Class Secretary's Records-S-T (Box 1819, Folder 15)
- Class Secretary's Records-V-Z (Box 1819, Folder 16)
- Reunions-Secretary's Notebooks 1909-1958 (Box 1820, Folder 1)
- Reunions 1914-1915 (Box 1820, Folder 2)
- Reunions 1923 (Box 1820, Folder 3)
- Reunions 1928 (Box 1820, Folder 4)
- Reunions 1933 (Box 1820, Folder 5)
- Reunions 1938 (Box 1820, Folder 6)
- Reunions 1948 (Box 1820, Folder 7)
- Reunions 1958 (Box 1821, Folder 1)
- Reunions-Composita Questionnaire 1958 (Box 1821, Folder 2)
- Reunions-Composita Questionnaire 1958 (Box 1821, Folder 3)
- Reunions-Composita Questionnaire 1958 (Box 1821, Folder 4)
- Reunions-Composita Questionnaire 1958 (Box 1821, Folder 5)
- Reunions 1963 (Box 1821, Folder 6)
- Reunions 1968 (Box 1821, Folder 7)
- Reunions 1973 (Box 1821, Folder 8)
- Reunions 1978 (Box 1821, Folder 9)
- Reunion Songs undated (Box 1821, Folder 10)
- Class Photographs 1913, 1926 (Box OV)
- Class Scrapbook, Photo Album (Box OV)
- Class Scrapbook, Reunion Memorabilia (Box OV)
- Reunion Memorabilia 1938 (Box OV)